Association on American Indian Affairs Records, 1851-2016 (bulk 1922-1995): Finding Aid MC147
Public Policy Papers
- Series 20: October 2016 Addition, 1925-2016; 10 boxes
  - Fundraising, 1994-2015; 1 box
    - Jonathan's Reports and Notes [re: Fundraising], 2012; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Solicitation Analysis, 2006-2008; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Solicitation Letter Proofs, 2007; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church, USA, 1994-1995; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Fidelity Charitable Gift Fund, 2004-2012; 1 box (Box 547)
    - First Catholic Slovak Ladies, 2009-2011; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Randy Motz Fundraising Effort Aid, 2015; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Blue Tahiti and Mailings, 2012-2013; 1 box (Box 547)
  - Scholarship Program, 2002-2015; 2 boxes
    - Scholarship Program, circa 2013-2015; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Scholarship Essays, 2013-2014; 1 box (Box 548)
      This folder is restricted. It will open in 2090.
    - 2015-2016 Scholarship Recipients, circa 2015; 1 box (Box 548)
      These folders are restricted. They will open in 2091.
    - Miscellaneous, circa 2003-2013; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Invited Students/Discontinued Students, circa 2012-2013; 1 box (Box 549)
      This folder is restricted. It will open in 2089.
    - Review Documentation, 2012-2015; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Budgets, 2004-2013; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Brochures, circa 2003-2013; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Forms, circa 2004-2010; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Reports, 2002-2011; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Board Meetings and Teleconferences, 2002-2014; 1 box (Box 548)
  - 2013-2014 Summer Camps, 1 box (Box 548)
  - Information Prepped for Faith's Perusal, undated; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Windy River [Donation], 2015; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Press Releases - Enewsletter/Newsletter, 2015; 1 box (Box 548)
  - IRP [Indigenous International Repatriation] Conference, 2015; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Newsletter Subscriptions, 2014; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Past Board Members, 2004; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Hard Copy/Forms, undated; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Website Posts, 2015; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Follow Up, 2014-2015; 1 box (Box 548)
  - [November Fundraising Event], 2013; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Annual Meeting Sign-In Sheet, undated; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Film Options [November Event], 2014; 1 box (Box 548)
  - [Meetings and Film Showcases], 2008-2012; 1 box (Box 548)
  - NCAI [National Congress of American Indians] Spring 2015, 1 box (Box 548)
  - [Miscellaneous Loose Papers], 2015; 1 box (Box 548)
  - Tax Exempt Form 501(c)(3) and 2014 Audit, 1989; 2015; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Tax Filings, 2005-2010; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Budget, 2009-2010; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Summer Camps, 2015; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Correspondence re: Death Notices, 2002; 2007; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Outside Inquiries, 2015; 1 box (Box 549)
    This folder is restricted. It will open in 2091.
  - Minute Book, 1994-2002; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Al Ketzler 50th Anniversary Tanana Chiefs, undated; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Board Nominees and Supplemental Board Nominees, undated; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Solicitation Examples, 2002-2007; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Panel on the Nonprofit Sector, 2005; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Socially Conscious Investing, 2010; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Nonprofit Legal Basics, 2004; 1 box (Box 549)
  - Employee Salary [and Budgets], 2005-2008; 1 box (Box 549)
    This folder is restricted. It will open in 2084.
- Series 21, Microfilms, dates not examined; 12 boxes (Box 558, Box 559, Box 560, Box 561, Box 562, Box 563, Box 564, Box 565, Box 566, Box 567, Box 568, Box 569)
  Arranged by series and reel number.
  Series 21 contains microfilms of files in Series 2 and Series 3.